<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Tools for hauling</name>
	<author>BBream</author>
	<targetVersion>Alpha 12d</targetVersion>
	<description>
  https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=12282.0
	Version V1.5a
	
  Contents List:
	- Cart for hauling
  - Backpack for hauling
  - Saddle for rider
		
  Change Log
  V1.5b
  - Texture is changed.
  - Bug is fixed.
  - Code is refined.
  
  V1.5a
  - 5 bugs are fixed. See this. https://github.com/BBream/ToolsForHaul/issues?q=is%3Aissue+is%3Aclosed
  - Animals can haul item depending on their body size. For example, muffalo has 2.0 body size and factor is 4.
  So, muffalo can haul 8 items. You can see body size in information window.(Carring capacity)
  
  V1.5
  - Cart and saddle can be mounted in animal's back. For this, Animal should be trained for 'Obeidence' and bigger than human.(baseBodySize >= 1.0)
  This is list of animal can mount cart and saddle: 
    Warg, Husky, LabradorRetriever, Elk, Thrumbo, Boomalope, Muffalo, Rhinoceros, Dromedary, Elephant, Cow, Alpaca.
  - Cart has been nerfed. Maximum items humanlike can haul with cart is changed from 6 items or 600 stacks to 3 items or 300 stacks. 
  Instead, Maximum items animal can haul with cart is 6 items or 600 stacks.
  - Saddle is added. Saddle can be mounted in animal's back. Human can board on Animal has saddle like riding horse. 
  Rider would attack if enemy is close enough.
  - 'Drop All' button is added in Cart's Gear inspector tab.
  
  V1.4b
  - Backpack bug is fixed. After just starting game and picking up backpack, error is occured.
  - Backpack bug is fixed. Hauling with backpack has problem when backpack is empty.
  - Now Colonist will check temperature is safe enough(80'C below) to do hauling job. 
  - Hauling with cart logic is changed. See https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=12282.msg175662#msg175662
  
  V1.4a
  - Backpack gizmo's drop floating menu bug is fixed. It was made disappear equipment try to drop.
  - Backpack is now used for hauling. Priority of using tool is Backpack - Cart - Hand.
    Before they start hauling with backpack, they will remember backpack's item that already put in and won't drop it.
  
  V1.4
  - Fixed for Alpha 12d
  
  V1.3a
  - Cargo renamed 'Cart'
  - Fixed for Alpha 11b
  
  V1.2a
  - Collecting and droping logic is changed. The colonist will collect and drop it while standing if it can reach in standing position.
  - Fixed bug that Cargo cannnot draw in while being carried by hand
  - Chunkslag may not print holder error message. If you see this error, please report me
  
  V1.2
  - Cargo is added new tab for filtering item. Cargo will be used just filtered item.
  - Cargo can be deconstructed by float menu button. It return 40 steels.
  - Korean language is available. Thanks Latta for translating.
  
  V1.1c
  - Save-load bug that try register new pawn if game is saved while hauling with cargo.
  
  V1.1b
  - Memory lick removed.

  V1.1a
  - Holder error message is not printed anymore.
  - Fixed backpack bug that cannot use and should reequip after loading game.
  
  V1.1
  - Backpack UI is improved.
  - Cargo now check storage priority.
  - Cargo Gizmo is removed.
  
  V1.0b
  - Cargo can store item in storage building.
  V1.0a
  - Cargo collect not just 6 items but also 600 stacks. it can collect 600 potatos.
  - Holder error message is fixed but still rarely printed. But it has no problem.
  - Fixed bug that colonist do not haul job even if haulable items exist.
    
	</description>
</ModMetaData>